( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
Wash your hands before eating.
You.
Uncle Houzi.
Did you take your medicine?
I'm pretty much recovered already.
See?
No.
You still need to take it for a few more months.
You know full well...
how awful that medicine tastes.
That's why...
you need to take it for a few more months.
I...
Did you take your medicine?
No.
Why not?
I feel I've been doing pretty well lately.
Go get your medicine.
The medicine's all gone.
Then go buy some.
Take her to buy some.
Let's go. Should be fine, right?
Are we out of medicine?
Looks like I need to hurry up...
and brew more special medicine.
Lord Zishu.
The one who came...
He... he isn't Su Yang.
Useless.
Though the one who came isn't Su Yang,
among these two,
there's a child named Tongtong.
She's the person Su Yang treasures most.
If we capture her,
Su Yang will naturally come to us.
See?
This should last a while.
I'm fine now.
But you...
The doctor said you still can't eat...
anything too oily or salty.
Good thing we came to the hospital,
otherwise the wound could easily get infected.
Are we really not going to look around?
We hardly ever get out of Black Street.
Let's go to the bathhouse for a massage,
or hit a karaoke lounge and sing.
Uncle Houzi's gotta show you the world today.
Uncle Houzi's got money.
We'll head east first.
Head east, then...
First place on the left at East Second Alley.
Number seven is the prettiest.
Qiushui Bathhouse has three basement floors,
right under the garage.
You need a VIP referral to get in.
At Huangducheng Karaoke Lounge,
just fold a ten-yuan bill and hand it to the front desk,
and you can unlock the door to a new world.
How do you know all this?
Uncle Sangou told me.
He loves going to these places.
He rambles about it so much my ears are getting calluses.
When you're better, he can take you there.
But for now...
we go home.
That Sangou...
really is a dog.
You know, some things...
you've gotta experience for yourself.
I said we're not going, so we're not.
If we head back this time,
there won't be another chance later.
Forget it.
Today's trip...
ends here.
Bosses.
You're just after money, right?
I know how things work on the streets.
I won't hide a single cent.
It's all here.
Listen...
let's just be friends today.
The card's PIN is 686868.
It's not much.
Consider it drinks on me, bosses.
What do you say, boss?
Since you're being reasonable,
you can leave.
The kid stays.
Don't, boss.
How much money can a kid even make you?
And she has cancer.
How about this?
I'll make a call...
and have more money sent over.
Okay, boss?
Boss.
Don't test my patience.
I'll give you three seconds.
If you don't leave,
then stay forever.
Three.
If I run away now,
I could still tip someone off.
Uncle Houzi.
Just go.
I'll be fine.
Nobody kills for no reason.
Two.
Go.
You...
One.
Already at one?!
Stay back, all of you!
Don't come any closer!
Uncle Houzi!
Good thing my speed and strength have improved lately.
You can't fight anymore!
Your wounds are splitting open!
I'll go with them.
Gentlemen.
I'm just a rat in the gutter.
I'm not worthy of opposing you.
Why don't we just drop this?
Let's...
let bygones be bygones.
After all...
if one of you slipped up...
and traded your life for trash like me,
it really wouldn't be worth it.
What's your name?
Shen... Shen Hou.
Shen Hou.
Shen Hou, the Monkey.
What an offensive name.
Uncle Houzi!
Tongtong!
Run, now!
I'll only have a chance to live if you run!
Run!
Don't you dare!
Uncle Houzi!
I find that mortals these days
are generally far too arrogant.
Move.
Let me go!
Let her go!
Uncle Houzi!
Foolish.
You think you can bargain with this immortal?
Let me go!
Uncle Houzi!
Although...
I don't know how Shen Hou,
the Monkey, is offensive at all.
But I do know this:
when my father gave me this name,
it was...
because he hoped I would...
become a Divine Monkey!
Alone, I can stride into the heavens,
and laugh at the petty fiends filling the sky.
My name is Qi Tian.
I am Qi Tian!
Qi Tian.
My staff dances across the heavens.
What a pity.
You only have brute strength.
Uncle Houzi!
Behave yourself!
Let me go!
Uncle Houzi!
Just a Remnant Soul.
Even after a thousand years,
it's still this powerful.
Lord Zishu.
We should retreat for now.
Such a big disturbance
will surely draw Shanhai City's people.
With our current strength,
we can't face them head-on yet.
Are you saying
this immortal can't beat those mortals?
No!
That's not what I meant at all.
Our target is Su Yang.
Until then,
we shouldn't risk any mishaps.
Besides, we've already captured Tongtong.
Now,
we just wait for Su Yang to walk right into his death.
Bunch of useless fools.
This high immortal isn't
as powerful as we imagined.
Tongtong.
Go get Madman.
I can't die yet.
I'm begging you.
Take me to Black Street.
Please, I'm begging you.
Yellow Springs Clinic.
I'll take you.
Come on.
Thank you.
The quality's pretty good.
Good stuff.
Isn't this guy one of Madman's people?
Didn't he go out with Tongtong this morning?
Where's Tongtong?
Su Yang isn't at the clinic.
We've got big trouble now.
Can you help me to that spot?
Sure.
That's my spot.
Take it slow.
How are you holding up?
Thank you.
I should've given you some money.
No need.
In the end,
I still couldn't escape.
In that situation,
as a grown man,
who could bear
to abandon a child?
Why play the hero?
Tongtong.
Captured.
In danger.
You should get more sunlight.
It'll heal your wounds faster.
No need.
I'll just sit here.
Sunlight is good for you.
I want some sun.
I really...
don't want to die.
I'm...
so afraid of dying.
The storyteller
roams everywhere.
Blood in every corner.
Madness in every corner.
I said
I'd never leave Black Street again.
I'm just a thief.
Why force me to fight?